Register of the Latvia Sutnieciba (Sweden) Records, 1917-1939
Hoover Institution Archives
Latvia Sutnieciba (Sweden) Records,
1917-1939
72067
Latvia. Sutnieciba (Sweden)
14 manuscript boxes (5.8 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Correspondence, memoranda, and reports, relating to Latvian foreign relations and to Latvian-Swedish relations. Records of the Latvian Embassy in Stockholm.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1972.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
Latvia.; Latvia--Foreign relations.; Latvia--Foreign relations--Sweden.; Sweden.; Sweden--Foreign relations--Latvia.
Series Description
- Correspondence of Embassy in Stockholm (Box No. 1-3.)
  Correspondence, arranged chronologically by year
- Instructions from the Ministry of Foreign Affairs to Embassy in Stockholm (Box No. 4.)
  Arranged chronologically by year
- Reports to the Ministry of Foreign Affairs from Embassy in Stockholm (Box No. 4.)
- Confidential Reports from the Latvian Embassies (Box No. 4-13.)
  Reports, arranged alphabetically by name of country
- Correspondence between Embassies and Ministry of Foreign Affairs (Box No. 13.)
- Treaties, Projects, etc. (Box No. 13.)
- Miscellaneous Documents (Box No. 14.)
  Miscellaneous documents, arranded alphabetically by subject
Container List
- CORRESPONDENCE OF EMBASSY IN STOCKHOLM
  - 1919 (Box 1.)
  - 1920
  - 1920-1922
  - 1921
  - 1921 (Box 2.)
  - 1922
  - 1923-1929
  - 1923-1929 (Box 3.)
  - 1926
  - 1927
  - 1931-1933
  - 1932
  - 1933
- INSTRUCTIONS FROM THE MINISTRY OF FOREIGN AFFAIRS TO EMBASSY IN STOCKHOLM
  - 1933-1935 (Box 3.)
  - 1933-1935 (Box 4.)
  - 1936-1937
  - 1931-1932
- REPORTS TO THE MINISTRY OF FOREIGN AFFAIRS FROM EMBASSY IN STOCKHOLM
  - 1938 (Box 4.)
- CONFIDENTIAL REPORTS FROM THE LATVIAN EMBASSIES
  - France, 1930-1931 (Box 4.)
  - France, 1933-1935
  - France, 1938
  - Austria, 1937 (Box 5.)
  - Argentina, 1938-1939
  - Brazil, 1931
  - Belgium, 1930-1932
  - Belgium, 1933-1935
  - Belgium, 1936
  - Belgium, 1937
  - Belgium, 1938
  - Belgium, 1939
  - Czechoslovakia, 1931
  - Czechoslovakia, 1933-1935
  - Czechoslovakia, 1938
  - England, 1930-1932
  - England, 1930-1932 (Box 6.)
  - England, 1933-1935
  - England, 1938-1939
  - Estonia, 1933-1935
  - Estonia, 1936
  - Estonia, 1937 (Box 7.)
  - Estonia, 1938
  - Estonia, 1939
  - Finland, 1932-1935
  - Finland, 1937
  - Finland, 1938
  - Finland, 1939
  - Germany, 1933-1935 (Box 8.)
  - Germany, 1936
  - Germany, 1937
  - Germany, 1938
  - Germany, 1939 (Box 9.)
  - Italy, 1930-1931
  - Itlay, 1933-1935
  - Italy, 1938-1939
  - League of Nations, 1931-1932
  - League of Nations, 1933-1935
  - League of Nations, 1938 (Box 10.)
  - Lithuania, 1937
  - Lithuania, 1938
  - Lithuania, 1939
  - Poland, 1933-1935
  - Poland, 1933-1935 (Box 11.)
  - Poland, 1935
  - Poland, 1938 (Box 12.)
  - United States, 1938
  - USSR, 1930-1932
  - USSR, 1933-1935
  - USSR, 1936
  - USSR, 1937
  - USSR, 1938
  - USSR, 1939 (Box 13.)
  - Miscellaneous countries, 1933-1934
  - Miscellaneous countries, 1933
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN LATVIAN EMBASSIES AND MINISTRY OF FOREIGN AFFAIRS
  - 1922-1923 (Box 13.)
- TREATIES, PROJECTS, ETC.
  - 1921-1922 (Box 13.)
  - 1922
- MISCELLANEOUS DOCUMENTS
  - Conferences of Ministers of Foreign Affairs (Box 14.)
  - Far East period, 1917-1918
  - Latvian Government's working day
  - Soviet-Latvian Army, Military Orders, 1919 and Latvian Saeima (Parliament), documents, 1923